<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fire Safety App</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome in our app. Here you can get fire safety info of your building.</string>
    <string name="q1">What is your building type?</string>
    <string-array name="building_type">
        <item>A: RESIDENTIAL</item>
        <item>B: EDUCATIONAL</item>
        <item>C: INSTITUTION FOR CARE</item>
        <item>D: HEALTH CARE FACILITIES</item>
        <item>E: BUSINESS</item>
        <item>F: MERCANTILE</item>
        <item>G: INDUSTRIAL</item>
        <item>H: STORAGE</item>
        <item>I: ASSEMBLY</item>
        <item>J: HAZARDOUS</item>
        <item>K: GARAGES</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="residential_types">
        <item>A1 and A2: Single Family Dwelling and Two Families Dwelling</item>
        <item>A3: Flats and Apartments</item>
        <item>A4: Mess, Boarding House and Hostels</item>
        <item>A5: Hotels and Lodging Houses</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="a1">(a) For low rise building fire detection and fixed firefighting arrangements shall not be required.
(b) High rise buildings exceeding each floor area 500 m2 shall have manual alarm system and portable
extinguishers provided in the escape stairs route or in fire lift lobby and as per provision of this Code.
(c) High rise buildings exceeding each floor area 500 m2 shall have manual alarm system and dry or wet riser
hydrant system per provision of this Code. [Ref. BNBC 2015 page: 4-48]</string>

    <string name="a3">(a) Up to 20 m height fire detection and fixed firefighting arrangement shall not be required.
(b) No protection required within the dwelling units of flats and apartments high rise buildings manual alarm
system and fixed hydrant system shall be provided in the landings of fire stairs or in the left lobby as per
provision of this Code shall be required. [Ref. BNBC 2015 page: 4-48]</string>


    <string name="a4">(a) For buildings up to 2 storey height, fire detection, fire alarm and fixed firefighting arrangements shall not be
required.
(b) Buildings having 3 stories and having floor area less than 300 m2 shall not require fire detection and fixed
firefighting arrangements.
(c) The floor area of 3 stories building having more than 300 m2 per floor and less than 33 m height having central
corridor with rooms on both sides, manual fire alarm system shall be provided along with portable fire
extinguishers. Instead of double loaded corridor a single loaded corridor having 3 m width shall not require
any detection and fixed firefighting arrangements.
(d) High rise boarding house, mess and hostels manually operated electric fire alarm system shall be provided
along with hydrant system. [Ref. BNBC 2015 page: 4-48]</string>

    <string name="a5">(a) For buildings up to 2 storey height, fire detection, fire alarm and fixed firefighting arrangements shall not be
required.
(b) Buildings having 3 floors or above and having floor area less than 300 m2 shall not require fire detection and
fixed firefighting arrangements.
(c) The floor area of such building is more than 300 m2 per floor and low rise building having central corridor with
rooms on both sides, manually operated fire alarm system shall be provided along with portable fire
extinguishers.
(d) High rise hotels and lodging houses manually operated electric fire alarm system shall be provided along with
hydrant system. [Ref. BNBC 2015 page: 4-48]</string>

    <string-array name="educational_types">
        <item>B1: Low Rise</item>
        <item>B2: High Rise</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="care_types">
        <item>C1: Institution for Care of Children</item>
        <item>C2: Custodial Institution for the Physically Capable adults</item>
        <item>C3: Custodial Institution for the Physically Incapable</item>
        <item>C4: Penal and mental institutions for children</item>
        <item>C5: Penal and mental institutions for adults</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="health_care_types">
        <item>D1: Normal Medical Facilities</item>
        <item>D2: Emergency Medical Facilities</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="business_types">
        <item>1. Office buildings up to 2 storey high and 500 m2 single effective undivided space in a floor</item>
        <item>2. Office buildings more than 2 storey high or more than 500 m2 single effective undivided space in a floor.</item>
        <item>3. Laboratories with precession instruments</item>
        <item>4. Control areas of office buildings dealing with flammable liquids.</item>
        <item>5. Solvent storage in a control area of an office</item>
        <item>6. Telecommunication, Internet gateway equipment or computer installation in an unattended server room.</item>
        <item>7. Electrical low tension distribution panel room in a sub-station.</item>
        <item>8. Space under one false ceiling more than 500 m2</item>
        <item>9. Essential Services</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mercantile_types">
        <item>1. Whole sale establishments, transport booking establishments</item>
        <item>2. Shopping arcade with central corridors open to sky</item>
        <item>3. Mercantile building under covered roof with single effective undivided space more than 500 m2 on each floor</item>
        <item>4. Underground mercantile structure</item>
        <item>5. Petrol pump and CNG station, automobile garages</item>
        <item>6. Aircraft hangars</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="industry_types">
        <item>G1: Low Hazard Industries</item>
        <item>G2: Moderate Hazard Industries</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="storage_types">
        <item>H1: Low Fire Risk Storage</item>
        <item>H2: Moderate Fire Risk Storage</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="assembly_types">
        <item>I1: Large Assembly with Fixed Seats</item>
        <item>I2: Small Assembly with Fixed Seats</item>
        <item>I3: Large Assembly without Fixed Seats</item>
        <item>I4: Small Assembly without Fixed Seats</item>
        <item>I5: Sports Facilities</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="subtype_req">Please provide appropriate Sub-type.</string>
    <string name="thanks">Thanks to use our app. Here are your result as BNBC (Bangladesh National Building Code), 2015. </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

</resources>